

# **DHARANIKUMAR K**

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 



#### CONTACT



#### **Phone**

+91-9952638437



#### **Email**

dharanfsd@gmail.com



#### **Address**

Dusi, Kancheepuram, Tamilnadu



### **MY SKILLS**

- O HTML
- (2) CSS
- O BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NODEJS
- EXPRESS JS
- () MONGODB



#### **PORTFOLIO**





### **PROFILE INFO**

To work with a progressive organization in which I can contribute my technical skills and experience to achieve the objectives of the organization with the attribute of time and quality at the same time to enhance my own productivity.

# C ....

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma In Automobile 2009-2011Engineering

Dusi Polytechnic College, Dusi

B.E - Mechanical Engineering2013-2016

Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College of Engineering. - AMACE Vadamavandhal-Kancheepuram

MBA - Supply Chain Management 2018-2019

University of Madras - Chennai

# CERTIFICATE

Full Stack Development 2022-2023

Guvi - Chennai

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Quality Trainee2011-2013

Hyundai Mobis - Chennai

Quality Engineer2016-2018

Rockman - Cheyyar

Quality Engineer2018-2019

TVS Sundaram Clayton - Chennai

Entrepreneur 2019-Till Now

STARFLIT- Dusi, Kancheepuram

# MY ACHIEVEMENT

- Reduce the Rejection 10% to 3% by process optimization in HPDC along with product design.
- O Conduct TS 16949: 2002 System Internal Audit, MRM.